ACTWU's Research Department Company Records 5619/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- GULF WESTERN. Annual Reports, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- GULF WESTERN. Plant Lists (Box 46, Folder 27)
- GULF WESTERN. Clippings, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- GULF WESTERN. Moyer Co. (Subsidiary of G & W), 1975 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- GULF WESTERN. Kayser-Roth Clippings (see also K-R), 1975 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Gumdrops, Inc., 1973 (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Gunnin Manufacturing Co., 1967 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- Gunst, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- Guntown Slacks, Inc., 1975 (Box 46, Folder 34)
- GURNEY INDUSTRIES, Inc. Botany Cottons Division, Gastonia, NC, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- GURNEY INDUSTRIES, Inc. Jewell Cotton Mills, Thomasville, NC, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 36)
- GURNEY INDUSTRIES, Inc. Botany Cottons Division, Prattville, AL, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 37)
- E. Gutman & Sons, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 38)
- Gutman-tans Glove Co., Inc., 1965 (Box 46, Folder 39)
- Gutman-Mayer Glove Co. (See also Kayser-Roth), 1968 (Box 46, Folder 40)
- Guy One, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 41)
- Gyula Designs, Inc., 1975 (Box 46, Folder 42)
- H & H Sportswear Co., 1971 (Box 46, Folder 43)
- H & L Pants Co., 1966 (Box 46, Folder 44)
- H & M Knitting Mills, Inc., 1970 (Box 46, Folder 45)
- H & M Neckwear Co., Inc., 1971 (Box 46, Folder 46)
- H & P Spool and Bobbin Co., 1982 (Box 46, Folder 47)
- H & S (Permicel Corp.), East Rutherford, NJ, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 48)
- H & S Optics, Altoona, PA, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 49)
- HCA Industries, Inc, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 50)
- HCA Industries, Inc Annual Reports, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
- HCA Industries, Inc News Clippings, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 52)
- HDL Liquidating Co., Inc. (See H. D. Lee Co.), 1969 (Box 46, Folder 53)
- H. F. Manufacturing Corp., 1971 (Box 46, Folder 54)
- H. I. I. Corp (See Henry I. Siegel), 1963 (Box 46, Folder 55)
- H. K. Corp, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 56)
- H. K. S., 1967 (Box 46, Folder 57)
- H. M. B. Originals, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 58)
- H. R. R. Co., Saxonville, MA, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 59)
- Hartfield - Zodys, Inc., 1976 (Box 46, Folder 60)
- Hartfield - Zodys, Inc. Annual Reports, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 61)
- Hartfield - Zodys, Inc. News Clippings, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 62)
- Haas Jordan Co., Toledo, Ohio, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 63)
- Hackensack Belt & Nut Co., Passaic, NJ, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 64)
- Hackleburg Manufacturing, Inc., 1967 (Box 46, Folder 65)
- Hagale Garment Co., 1968 (Box 46, Folder 66)
- David Hagan & Co., Inc. (See Puntan Sportswear), 1961 (Box 46, Folder 67)
- Hagarth Manufacturing Co., 1967 (Box 46, Folder 68)
- Hale Brothers Associates, Inc., 1968 (Box 46, Folder 69)
- Halifax Knitting of South Boston, VA, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 70)
- Hall-Brown, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 71)
- Hall Tale Manufacturing Co. (See Breezy Wynn), 1956 (Box 46, Folder 72)
- Halle Bros, Inc., Cleveland, Ohio, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 73)
- Hallmark Shirt Co., Inc., 1961 (Box 46, Folder 74)
- Halpern Star Neckwear Co., Inc., 1953 (Box 46, Folder 75)
- Halsey, Ltd., 1973 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Halton & Sons, Philadelphia, PA, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Hamblet Machine Co., Lawrence, MA, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Hamburgers, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Hamilton Clothes, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Hamilton Short Company, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Hamilton Tailoring Company, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Hammond Corp., 1970 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Hammond Garment Manufacturing Co., Inc., Hammond, LA, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Hammond Organ Company, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Hammonton Park Clothes, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Hampco Apparel, Inc., 1974 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Hampshire Casuals, Ltd., New York, NY, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- John Hampton, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Hampton Looms of Virginia Labor II, 1958-1972 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Hamrick Mills, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Hamurnat Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Hancock George Textiles, Cambridge, Ontario, Canada, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Joe Handelsman & Sons, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Handi-Craft Co., (Subs of Swing-a-Way Manufacturing Co.), 1971 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Handleman Company, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Hang Out Corp., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Harold Co., 1970 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Hanover Shirt Co., 1966 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Hanover Togs, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Hansen Glove Corp., 1970 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- HANES Corp. (formerly P. H. Hanes Hosiery) Winston-Salem, NC. Financial, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- HANES Corp. (formerly P. H. Hanes Hosiery) Winston-Salem, NC. Labor, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- HANES Corp. (formerly P. H. Hanes Hosiery) Winston-Salem, NC. Clippings (Consolidated Foods), 1972 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- HANES Corp. (formerly P. H. Hanes Hosiery) Winston-Salem, NC. Drying & Finishing Co., 1972 (Box 47, Folder 30)
- Hanes of Canada, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 31)
- Happ, Inc., 1963 (Box 47, Folder 32)
- Harbrooke Clothes, LTD, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 33)
- Hardwick & Mager Carpet Co., 1971 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Hart, Schaffner & Marx, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 35)
- AA Midwest Company, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- ACD Manufacturing Co., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- A & F Originals, Inc., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- A & H, Inc., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- A-H Molded Products, Inc., 1976 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- A/L Sports, Inc., 1976 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- APF Electronics, Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Abercrombie & Fitch Co., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Able Company, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Acapulco Fashions of Texas, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Accurate Felt & Gasket Company, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Ace Manufacturing Co., 1973 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Acme Cotton Products, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Acme Leather Sportswear, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Action-Line, Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Action Time, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Active Place, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 17)
- Adirondack Wire & Cable Company, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 18)
- Adler's & Adler Leather Sportswear, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 19)
- Aigner, G. J. Co, Inc., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 20)
- Ahler's (Group) Pioneer, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 21)
- Affiliated Metal Products, Ltd., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 22)
- Aerofab, Inc., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 23)
- Adventure International, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 24)
- Advanced Quilting, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 25)
- Alben Manufacturing Company, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 26)
- Albert's. Inc. - Alcove Division, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 27)
- Alberto-Culver Company, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 28)
- Alco Standard Corp. (formerly Synthane Taylor Corp.), 1978 (Box 75, Folder 29)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. (Box 75, Folder 30)
- Allen Industries, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 31)
- Allied Textile Printers, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 32)
- Allis-Chalmers Corp. (American Air Filter Co., Inc.), 1979 (Box 75, Folder 33)
- Alloy Steel Tank & Welding Co., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 34)
- Almar Manufacturing Co., 1975 (Box 75, Folder 35)
- Altamont Garment Co., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 36)
- American Air Filter Co., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 37)
- American Bisque Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 38)
- American Brand Textile Corp., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 39)
- American Decal & Manufacturing Co., 1968 (Box 75, Folder 40)
- American Display Manufacturing, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 41)
- American Enka (1959 Organizing Campaign) (Box 75, Folder 42)
- American Home Products Corp., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 43)
- American Quilt Cover Manufacturing Corp., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 44)
- American Thermostat Corp., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 45)
- American White Cross Labs., 1971 (Box 75, Folder 46)
- Ames Discount Department Stores, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 47)
- Andala Company, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 48)
- Andmore Sportswear, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 49)
- Angus Garment Manufacturing Company, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 50)
- Angwell Corporation, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 51)
- Angwell Curtain Co. of Indiana, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 52)
- Anken Industries (See General Photo & Rochester Film), 1975 (Box 75, Folder 53)
- Ankokus Dyeing & Finishing Co., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 54)
- Ano Packing (Packaging) Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 55)
- Anthracite Shirt Co., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 56)
- Apex Decorators, Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 57)
- Apex Textile Printing Co., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 58)
- Appalachian Corporation, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 59)
- Apparel Industries of California (Subsidiary of Kayser Roth), 1978 (Box 75, Folder 60)
- Apparels, Inc., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 61)
- Appendages, Inc., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 62)
- Archrock Paving and Construction Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 63)
- Ari Industries, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 64)
- Arizona Fashions, Inc., 1975 (Box 75, Folder 65)
- Arizona Slack Corp., 1969 (Box 75, Folder 66)
- Ark Manufacturing, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 67)
- Arkay Pants Company, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 68)
- Armstrong Rubber Company, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 69)
- Aronsohn, Samuel, Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 70)
- Artistic Laces, Inc., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 71)
- Artistic Manufacturing Co., 1975 (Box 75, Folder 72)
- Asco, Inc., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 73)
- Aspen Skiwear, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 74)
- Aspro, Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 75)
- Associated Dry Goods Corp., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 76)
- Associated Merchandising Corp., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 77)
- Associated Products, Inc., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 78)
- Athlone Industries, Inc., 1975 (Box 75, Folder 79)
- Atlanta La Salle Corporation, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 80)
- Atlantic Sportswear, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 81)
- Auerbach International, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 82)
- Aurora Bleachery, Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 83)
- Austin Hill, Ltd., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 84)
- Auto-iron Products Corp., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 85)
- AVC Corp., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 86)
- Avante Associates, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 87)
- Avanti Knitting Mills, Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 88)
- Avtex Fibers, Inc., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 89)
- B & B Lorrys, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 90)
- BMB Affiliates, Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 91)
- BVD Co. Ltd., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 92)
- Babyworld Company, Inc., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 93)
- Baker Clothes, Inc, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 94)
- Balabaskins, Ltd., 1973 (Box 75, Folder 95)
- Balin Manufacturing Co. (Canada), 1964 (Box 75, Folder 96)
- Ball Stores, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 97)
- Baltimore Garment Company, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 98)
- Bamberger-Reinthal Co., Inc., 1970 (Box 75, Folder 99)
- Bancroft Licensing Division of Indian Head, Inc., 1968 (Box 75, Folder 100)
- Bangor Clothing Co., Inc., 1971 (Box 75, Folder 101)
- Bangor Punta Algre Sugar Corp., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 102)
- Bank Street Clothes, Inc. (Box 75, Folder 103)
- Barkers Discount Department Stores, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 104)
- Barnes Worsted Mill, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 105)
- Baroness Leather Products, Inc., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 106)
- Bass, J. & Company, Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 107)
- Baton Rouge Knitting, Inc., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 108)
- Battelstein's, Inc., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 109)
- Baxter, Kelly, Faust, Inc., 1976 (Box 75, Folder 110)
- Bay Island Industries, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 111)
- Bayco, Inc., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 112)
- Baycor, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 113)
- Beaunit Corp. (Statesville, SC), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Beaunit Corp. (form. Beaunit Mills) (Folder II Financial1970-1974) (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Becker Electronics Corp., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Becton, Dickenson & Co., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Before Six, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Behrens, H. Manufacturing Company, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Belair Fashions, Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Belding Corticelli, Ltd., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Bonne Bell, Inc., 1973 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Belnont Garment Co., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Belmont Sportswear, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Belting Co., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Bendel, Henri, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Bendetta Sportswear, Inc., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- Benje, Ltd., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Beno Manufacturing Corp., 1973 (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Berks Underwear, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 17)
- Bernard Screen Printing Corp., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 18)
- Bernat Laboratories, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 19)
- Bernice Industries, Inc., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 20)
- Bernson (Silk) Mills, Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 21)
- Bershan Clothes (See Louis Goldsmith), 1968 (Box 76, Folder 22)
- Besco Clothes, Inc., 1968 (Box 76, Folder 23)
- Besco Enterprises, Inc., 1968 (Box 76, Folder 24)
- Best Coat & Apron Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 25)
- Best Uniform Company, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 26)
- Better Backers, Inc., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 27)
- Bettina Underwear, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 28)
- Big Valley Industries, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 29)
- Biltwell Umbrella Co, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 30)
- Bird Knit, Inc., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 31)
- Birnbaum Bros., Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 32)
- Blake, Justin, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 33)
- Blue Ridge Textile, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 34)
- Blye International, Ltd., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 35)
- Bobbie Brooks Division of Colebrook Mills, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 36)
- Bodner Neckwear Co., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 37)
- Bogs, R. G., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 38)
- Bohack, H. C. Company (Supermarket Chain), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 39)
- Boland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 40)
- Bolivar Manufacturing Co., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 41)
- Bollag & Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 42)
- Bonita Leather Fashions, Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 43)
- Bonnier Fornag A. B. (Box 76, Folder 44)
- Bonitt Teller, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 45)
- Born, M. & Co., 1975 (Box 76, Folder 46)
- Borough of Glen Rock, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 47)
- Botany Shirt Co., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 48)
- Bottoms Up (Box 76, Folder 49)
- Boyd's, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 50)
- Boyle-Midway, Inc. (Subsidiary of American Home Products Corp.), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 51)
- Bradford Manufacturing, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 52)
- Brand-Rex Company (Subsidiary of American Enka/Akzona, Inc.), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 53)
- Brand X Fashions, Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 54)
- Brands Glove Corp., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 55)
- Brandord Trouser Co., Ltd., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 56)
- Brascan, Ltd., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 57)
- Brawer Bros., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 58)
- Brehm & Sons, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 59)
- Brehm & Staley, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 60)
- Bridgewater Manufacturing Co., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 61)
- Bridon Cordage, Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 62)
- Bristol-Myers Company, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 63)
- Brittania Neckwear, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 64)
- Brock Candy Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 65)
- Brodar, Eric, Enterprises, Inc., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 66)
- Bronzini, Ltd. (Subsidiary of Rockower Bros., Inc.), 1976 (Box 76, Folder 67)
- Brooke Industries, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 68)
- Brookfield Athletic Shoe Co., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 69)
- Brown, T. N. Industries, Inc., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 70)
- Brown & Williamson Tobacco Corp., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 71)
- Browning Dust Collector, Inc., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 72)
- Bruck Mills, Ltd., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 73)
- Brumby Textile Mills, Inc., 1968 (Box 76, Folder 74)
- Brunswick of Lumbertown, Inc., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 75)
- Buckaneer Sportswear (Subsidiary of Palm Beach), 1979 (Box 76, Folder 76)
- Buckley Pete and Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 77)
- Bullets Cutting Sys., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 78)
- Burkart Randall (Missouri)--(Division of Textron, Inc.), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 79)
- Burkart Randall (California)--(Division of Textron, Inc.), 1971 (Box 76, Folder 80)
- Burmill Trading Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 81)
- Busy B Manufacture Co., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 82)
- C & V Fabrics, Inc. (Subsidiary Girlie & Co.), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 83)
- C. B. S. Apparel Corp., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 84)
- C. I. Industries, Ltd., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 85)
- C. M. T. Industries, Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 86)
- C. P. I. Corporation (Subsidiary of Whittaker Corp,), 1979 (Box 76, Folder 87)
- C. P. M., Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 88)
- Cabinet Systems, Inc., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 89)
- Cadillac Shirt Corp. (Cadillac Industries - Garment Corporation of America), 1969 (Box 76, Folder 90)
- Caledonia, Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 91)
- California Carpet Finishing Co., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 92)
- California Casualaire, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 93)
- California Computer Products, Inc., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 94)
- Calspun Mills, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 95)
- Cam Manufacturing Co., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 96)
- Camp 7 Inc., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 97)
- Canadian Imperial Bank of Commerce, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 98)
- Canoe Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 99)
- Can-Tex Industries, Inc. (Subsidiary Harsco Corp.), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 100)
- Canton Textile Mills, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 101)
- Cape Cod Clothing Co., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 102)
- Capital Pants Co., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 103)
- Capital Quilting Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 104)
- Capitol Plastics of Ohio, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 105)
- Capri processing Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 106)
- Capture Me, Ltd., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 107)
- Cardin, Pierre, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 108)
- Caribe Leather Co., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 109)
- Carilee, Inc., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 110)
- Carl-Stan Curtain Manufacturing, Inc., 1971 (Box 76, Folder 111)
- Carlyle Industries, Inc., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 112)
- Carriage Club Corp., 1968 (Box 76, Folder 113)
- Carrier Corporation, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 114)
- Carrier Footwear Corp., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 115)
- Carrington Viyella Yarns, Inc., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 116)
- Carson Pirie Scott & Co., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 117)
- Carson, Johnny, Division of M. Wile & Sons. (Box 76, Folder 118)
- Cartaret Products Co., Inc., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 119)
- Cashiers Plastic Corp., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 120)
- Casket Shells, Inc., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 121)
- Casser Overseas Corporation, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 122)
- Cassini, Oleg, Clothes for Gentlemen, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 123)
- Cathedral Envelope Company (Subsidiary of Columbia Corp.), 1976 (Box 76, Folder 124)
- Cato Show Printing Cop., Inc., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 125)
- Cedar Throwing Mills, Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 126)
- Champlain Clothes, Ltd., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 127)
- Chandler Yarns, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 128)
- Chaps Sportswear, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 129)
- Chemetron Corp., 1973 (Box 76, Folder 130)
- Cheri-Alan, Ltd., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 131)
- Cherokee Industries, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 132)
- Chester Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1968 (Box 76, Folder 133)
- Chromascope, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 134)
- Churchill, N. Manufacturing Co., Inc. (Churchill Glove), 1979 (Box 76, Folder 135)
- Churchill, C. S. & Co., Inc. (Subsidiary of Greif & Co.), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 136)
- Cincinnati Industries, Inc., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 137)
- City Investing Company, Inc., 1975 (Box 76, Folder 138)
- City Stores Company, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 139)
- Clark, C & J Ltd., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 140)
- Clark-Cutler-McDermott Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 141)
- Clarkton Mills, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 142)
- Classic Weaving Corp., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 143)
- Clearview Textile Corp., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 144)
- Cleve Shirtmakers, Inc., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 145)
- Cliche, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 146)
- Clinton Swan Clothes, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 147)
- Clopay Corp., 1977 (Box 76, Folder 148)
- Clow Corporation, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 149)
- Coastal Industrial, Inc., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Cobb, Jeremy, Co., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Coburn Corp. of America, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Codell Casuals, Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Cohen, I & B, Bomzon Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Coley Footwear, Inc., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Coleman Clothes, Inc., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Collins & Alkman Corp., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Colonial Container Corp., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Colonial Corp. of America (Annual Reports) (Merged with Kayser Roth), 1967 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Colonial Printing Ink, Inc., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Columbia Mills, Inc., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Columbian Rope Company (Plymouth Cordage Division) (Financial & General), 1974 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Columbian Rope Company (Plymouth Cordage Division) (New Orleans, LA), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Columbus Outdoor Advertising Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Commercial Affiliates, Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Commercial Flocking, Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- Conagra, Inc., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 18)
- Concept Industries, Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 19)
- Concorde International Apparel, Ltd., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 20)
- Connie Sportswear, Inc., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 21)
- Consolidated Wafer & Cone Corp., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 22)
- Constellation Canada Co., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 23)
- Consumer Industries, Inc., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 24)
- Consumers Manufacturing Co., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 25)
- Continental Fashion Imports, Inc., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 26)
- Continental Screen Printing Corp., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 27)
- Cook United, Inc., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 28)
- Cooper Mattress Manufacturing Co. (Subsidiary Kingsdown, Inc.), 1978 (Box 77, Folder 29)
- Corah Limited, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 30)
- Cordelle Uniform Co., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 31)
- Cortefiel de Espana (See Tri Sportswear), 1976 (Box 77, Folder 32)
- Cosdon Oil & Chemical Co., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 33)
- Cosell Casuals, Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 34)
- Craft Rug Mill, Inc., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 35)
- Crane Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 36)
- Cranston Print Works (Qualitex Division), 1978 (Box 77, Folder 37)
- Creamery Company of Huntington, Inc., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 38)
- Creations by Kenscott, Inc., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 39)
- Cresbury Clothes, Inc., 1973 (Box 77, Folder 40)
- Cross River Products, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 41)
- Crouse-Hinds Co., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 42)
- Crowell Cap Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 43)
- Cumberland Apparel Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 44)
- Custom Dental Laboratories of Mt. Vernon, NY, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 45)
- Cye-Frank, Inc., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 46)
- D'Andri, Roberto (Division of Mac Muller), 1976 (Box 77, Folder 47)
- Daber, Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 48)
- Daire, W. F. Co. (Division of Farah), 1976 (Box 77, Folder 49)
- Dan River, Inc. (Webco Mills & Webco Dyers Divisions), 1978 (Box 77, Folder 50)
- Dan Dee Belt & Bag Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 51)
- Danfield Threads, Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 52)
- Danor Enterprises, Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 53)
- Danubia Mills, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 54)
- Danzero, Inc., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 55)
- Darling Stores Corp, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 56)
- Darobspun, Inc., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 57)
- Davis Can Co. (Subsidiary of Van Dorn Co.), 1978 (Box 77, Folder 58)
- Davis Manufacturing Co., 1973 (Box 77, Folder 59)
- Daylin Corp., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 60)
- Day's Inn, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 61)
- Dayton Corp., 1969 (Box 77, Folder 62)
- Dayton Electric Manufacturing Co. (Subsidiary of W. W. Grainger, Inc.), 1976 (Box 77, Folder 63)
- Dayton Hudson Corp., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 64)
- Debenham's, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 65)
- Deerfield Manufacturing Co., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 66)
- Defiance Bleachery, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 67)
- De La Renta, Oscar, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 68)
- Dell Industries, Inc., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 69)
- Delta Knitting Mills, Inc., 1974 (Box 77, Folder 70)
- Delta Manufacturing Corp., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 71)
- Delton Formal Wear, Inc., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 72)
- Dempsey Textile Rental Services, Inc., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 73)
- Denison Cotton Mill Co., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 74)
- Derry Limestone Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 75)
- Detroit Institute of Laundries & Linen, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 76)
- Dial Tuxedos, Inc., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 77)
- Diamond Shamrock Corp., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 78)
- Diana Sportswear, Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 79)
- Dickey Oakwood, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 80)
- Diolinda Sportswear, Inc., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 81)
- Dixie Yarns, Inc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 82)
- Dobbie Industries, Ltd., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 83)
- Dollar General Corp., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 84)
- Domstrand (Silk Mills) Limited, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 85)
- Donegal, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 86)
- Donlin Sportswear, Inc., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 87)
- Donnelly, R. R. & Sons Co., 1979 (Box 77, Folder 88)